音频作者已去除对话（采用Narokath分享的音频）
Friendship used to make me so queasy, queasy
友谊曾经让我 畏惧远离
But you made it all so easy, easy
你们让它变得 简单容易
Now I don't have to say what I'm thinking
脑海中有想法 初见端倪
You already know without even blinking
大家却早已经 心有灵犀
You girls are the apple of my eye
你们是我眼中小苹果
The race that doesn't end in a tie
犹如赛场上激情似火
You are the funnel cake at my fair
香甜好似蛋糕别错过
The warm hug of a fuzzy bear
像毛绒熊抱真暖和
Best friends until the end of time
友谊 永远不离不弃
We'll have each other's backs
相互支持鼓励
And let our true selves shine
秀出真实自己
And that's because everything we need
真谛就在 世上无难题
is all right here
只要你有
When we're with our team
队友陪伴你
音频作者已去除对话（采用Narokath分享的音频）
I simply can't imagine there'd be a day
不敢想象有一天 我会放弃
Where I wouldn't want to be walking your way
与好朋友共处的 一点一滴
Whatever new problems there may be, may be
无论眼前会遭遇 什么难题
Our friendship is always the door with a key
开门钥匙永远是 真挚友谊
You are the jewels in my friendship crown
你们是我掌上的瑰宝
The sparks that make my world go 'round
让我的世界更加闪耀
We bring the best out, that's our goal
一起尽全力奔向目标
There's no telling how far we'll go
友谊的旅伴心气高
Best friends until the end of time
友谊 永远不离不弃
We'll have each other's backs
相互支持鼓励
And let our true selves shine
秀出真实自己
And that's because everything we need
真谛就在 世上无难题
is all right here
只要你有
When we're with our team
队友陪伴你